<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KUBE2GO.io Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.kube2go.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KUBE2GO.io Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.kube2go.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving Kube2go</title>
      <link>http://blog.kube2go.io/post/retirement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kube2go.io/post/retirement/</guid>
      <description>Kube2go Moving to Sandbox
Thanks for all the support you have given tot Kube2go for the better part of the year. With Kube2go we saw interest from all kinds of developers and enterprises alike and received valuable feedback. As part of our efforts to make customer experience better we are consolidating Platform9&amp;rsquo;s Sandbox (https://platform9.com/sandbox/) and Kube2go into one system and retiring Kube2go as an independent service.
We hope Platform9 Sandbox would offer you much more than Kube2go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing KUBE2GO</title>
      <link>http://blog.kube2go.io/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 11:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kube2go.io/post/about/</guid>
      <description>Announcing Kube2go
At Platform9, we have not only made containers a core part of our overall product strategy, but have also gone all-in with Kubernetes as the container orchestration framework of choice. Over the last couple of years, as Kubernetes has risen to become the most popular container orchestration engine, it has been great to see the community come together and work towards making it successful. As our own small effort to aid this growth, we are very proud, today, to announce Kube2Go to the Kubernetes community – the easiest way to run Kubernetes clusters on any major public cloud!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>